Name: Shrijan Tiwari Address: 42 Thornleigh Road, Jesmond, Newcastle Upon Tyne, United Kingdom

Postal Code: NE2 3ET Mobile Number: +44 07436603316 Email: shrijansoftware39@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Graduated Master of Science in Computer Game Engineering from Newcastle University. I have over 4 years of work experience as a Front End Developer/Software Developer. My Technical Skills are JavaScript, Unreal Engine, Unity, TypeScript, Angular, Lua, C++, C#, React, Vue.js, LESS, Bootstrap, OpenGL, Java, SASS, HTML, CSS, Strapi CMS, MySQL, Blender, jQuery and Node.js.

Link to my Portfolio – https://shrijan42.github.io/

Employment History

September 2022 - Present

Front-End Software Developer - Motivait (Newcastle upon Tyne, United Kingdom)

- Working as a Front-End Software Developer in projects such as Newcastle Helix, Motivait CMS and FFDT using JavaScript, Angular 14, TypeScript, Strapi CMS, Mysql, Node.js and SASS. Six Months into the job currently working as a Full Stack Developer for 3 Motivait projects such as Newcastle Helix, Motivait CMS and FFDT.
- Working as a Front-End Software Developer using Javascript, Angular JS, Angular 13, TypeScript, Mysql and Node.js in projects such as Zebra Island, Grainger Market, Zebra Dashboard and BUS1016.

October 2018-March 2020

Front End Developer/Software Developer - Olive Group (HiUp Solutions) (Nepal/Head Office:Ireland)

- Develop and enhance frontend platform website/web application/API for Connected Portfolio-Premier-Education-Group, Document Management System and Apprenticeship Management.
- Design and develop new front end application for various platforms. Help out with front-end work on other application (HTML/CSS/Javascript/Vue/Angular in Node.js applications.)

March 2018-August 2018

Front End Developer/Software Developer-Deerwalk Inc (Nepal/Head Office:U.S.A.)

- Design and develop new front end application for Plan Analytics and other big data solutions based on U.S. health care sector.
- Feature, Support, Bug and Report Task in Deerwalk's Plan Analytics application and Executive Analytics applications using Javascript, Bootstrap, Java and Angular.

January 2017-November 2017

Web Developer/Front End Developer -Deerwalk Group Ltd. (Nepal/Head Office:U.S.A.)

 Design and Develop web application for Deerwalk which includes Deerwalk Institute of Technology website, Deerwalk CTEVT website, Deerwalk Library Management System and Hospital Management System web application using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Angular, Bootstrap, Typescript and SASS.

Education

Master of Science in Computer Game Engineering (September 2021- September 2022) (Date of Graduation: December 7 2022) – Newcastle University

Grade - Distinction

- CSC8501 : Advanced Programming for Games
- CSC8502 : Advanced Graphics for Games
- o CSC8503: Advanced Game Technologies
- CSC8507 : Game Technology Innovations
- CSC8508: Engineering Gaming Solutions within a Team
- CSC8599: Project and Dissertation in Computer Game Engineering

Bachelor of Science (Hons) in Computing (September 2014- September 2017) (Date of Graduation: December 4 2017) - Islington College (London Metropolitan University)

Grade - Second Class Honours

Key Skills (Technical Skills)

HTML	C++	OpenGL	Node.js
CSS	C#	Blender	
JavaScript	Unity	MySQL	
TypeScript	Unreal Engine	CMS Strapi	
Angular	Lua	LESS	
Bootstrap	Java	SASS	
Vue.js	React	jQuery	

Languages

Nepali (Native or Fluent), English (Native or Fluent), Hindi (Native or Fluent), Urdu (Full professional proficiency), German (Beginner)